翻译  小饭
翻译  小暴徒
翻译  丶Charl
翻译  杏仁斯嘉丽
翻译  ET外星人
翻译  珈美
翻译  江湖人称王姑娘
翻译  沫沫
时间轴  小式
顾问  老杜
后期  饿得慌
校对  草草
总监  草草
第四季  第十一集
纸牌屋
人人影视倾情奉献
两位安德伍德进驻白宫
安东尼·莫雷蒂纪念基金
弗莱迪
烧烤餐馆
安德伍德夫妇
安德伍德总统夫妇今日返回路易斯安那州
President and Mrs. Underwood are back in Louisiana today,
为争取获得...
in an effort to pick up...
安德伍德今天来到拉斯维加斯
Underwood is in Las Vegas today,
与烹饪工会的领导人会面
meeting with leadership from the Culinary Union...
今天下午在查尔斯顿
...questions from undecided voters
回答游离选民的提问
in Charleston this afternoon,
这是今天三项安德伍德竞选活动的第一项
the first of three events the Underwood campaign...
第一夫人今天在卡斯珀一市政厅集会上接受提问
The First Lady took questions at a town hall meeting in Casper today.
安德伍德夫妇6天就走了12个城市
That's 12 cities in half as many days for the Underwoods.
同时  他们仍在所有全国民调中
Meanwhile, they still trail Conway by 12
落后于康威12到14个百分点
to 14 points in every national poll.
这个差距并不小
That's a big gap to close...
博伊西的支持者比原计划多等了总统两小时
...supporters in Boise waited an extra two hours for the president...
总统在俄亥俄州的竞选活动将会...
The president's whistle-stop tour of Ohio will...
你们就是能决定这一切的州之一
You're one of the states that will decide this!
今天下午在查尔斯顿
...took questions from undecided voters
回答游离选民的提问  这是今天三项...
in Charleston this afternoon, the first of three events...
请以波士顿式的热情欢迎我们的下任总统
Please give a big Boston welcome to the next president...
对很多美国人来说  问题依然在于
For many Americans, the question remains,
一个双安德伍德式的白宫会是什么样
what would an Underwood-Underwood White House look like?
安德伍德夫妇二人都...
Both Underwoods have courted--
周一去亚利桑那州  内华达州和加州
So, Arizona, Nevada, and California on Monday,
周二去中西部地区的州
then the upper Midwest on Tuesday.
还不够  康威去的州比我们多多了
It's not enough. Conway's hitting way more states than we are.
他又不是在任总统  比你有更多时间
Well, he's not a sitting president. He has more time than you do.
那我们就得挤出更多时间
Well, then we have to make more time.
我们必须到各地去  我们必须动...
We have to get out there. We've got to shake--
弗兰西斯  你还好吗
Francis, are you okay?
-我没事  -坐一会儿吧
- I'm fine. - Sit down for a moment.
不不  我没事  我没事  我们继续
No, no, I'm fine, I'm fine. Let's continue.
如果您想在加州多安排一场筹款活动
If you wanna add a fundraiser in California,
这个没问题
we can make that happen.
好吧
Okay.
怎么样
So?
我同意撒克逊医生和医疗团队的建议
I agree with Dr. Saxon and the medical team.
我们得把飞行次数减到一周一次
We should reduce air travel to once a week.
恐怕那不可能
I'm afraid that's not possible.
您想听其他人的建议  先生  这就是
You wanted a second opinion, sir. You have it.
我不是想听别人的建议  我是想听不同的建议
I didn't want a second opinion. I wanted a different opinion.
飞机对您有伤害
Planes take a toll.
我们担心突发器官排斥
We're concerned about a sudden organ rejection.
如果我不四处跑  我就无法赢得选举
I can't win an election if I can't travel.
如果您住院了  也赢不了
You can't win if you're hospitalized.
谢谢你  医生
Thank you, Doctor.
你留下来  康威去哪我就去哪  我会..
You stay here. I'll go wherever Conway goes, I'll just--
是我竞选总统  我必须亲自去
I'm on the top of the ticket. It has to be me.
我们不能无视医生的建议  弗兰西斯
We can't ignore the doctors, Francis.
宣传是关键
It's the story we tell.
如果我留在这里  而康威到处奔走
If I stay here, Conway prances around the country,
标榜他的战斗机飞行员形象  与此同时
playing up his fighter-pilot image, and meanwhile,
-我却困在玫瑰园里  -我不能冒险失去你
- I'm stuck here in the Rose Garden-- - I won't risk losing you.
我们得明智点
Let's be smart about this.
-我得表现出力量  -那就去表现
- I need to project strength. - So project it.
空袭正在起效  先生
The air strikes are working, sir.
我们已经阻止了哈里发国进入幼发拉底河
We've stopped ICO's advance to the Euphrates.
只是延缓了进军  没有阻止
We've delayed the advance. We haven't stopped it.
你们的报告说他们在重新集结
Your own reports say they're regrouping.
我需要一次决定性打击
I want a decisive blow,
抓人  领导人  传达一个讯息
a face, the leadership, to send a message.
艾哈迈迪兄弟躲起来了
Uh, the Ahmadi brothers are in hiding.
我们不知道他们的藏身之处
We don't know their location.
你们的任务就是找到他们
Well, your task is to find them.
我们努力了  先生
We've tried, sir.
我们的特工毫无进展
Our assets hit a wall.
要彻底铲除就得排遣特种部队去那里
To root them out would require special forces on the ground.
这也不是不可以
That is a step I am willing to take.
我们没有叙利亚的授权
We don't have authorization from the Syrians.
国务卿杜兰特会摆平这件事
Secretary Durant will smooth that out.
我不会满足于
I will not be satisfied
阻挡毒蛇的去路  先生们
by blocking the serpent's path, gentlemen.
我要砍掉它该死的脑袋
I wanna cut off its goddamn head.
叙利亚人会拒绝  到那时
The Syrians will say no, and when they do,
看看他们是否愿跟俄罗斯特种部队合作
see if they'll work with the Russian special forces.
脏活让俄罗斯人去干  我们坐收功劳
The Russians do the dirty work, we take all the credit.
佩特罗夫不会同意的
Petrov won't go for that.
还给他们几个钻井就会答应了
Well, he will if we give him back some of our drilling zones.
那需要国会的批准
Well, that'll take congressional approval.
道格正为此做准备
Doug's laying the groundwork now.
关于这件事你想听听我的意见
Are you interested in my opinion on this,
还是已经做好了决定
or has it already been decided?
我想迅速行动
I want to move fast,
所以除非你有更迅速的办法
so unless you have a quicker option,
不然最好还是保留观点吧
it's probably best you keep it to yourself.
-是  先生  -凯茜
- Yes, sir. - Cathy.
有什么问题吗
Do we have a problem?
没有  先生  我去和道格协调
No, sir. I'll coordinate with Doug.
被狗咬了以后  要么就把它干掉
After a dog's bitten you, you either put it to sleep,
要么就给它带上口套
or you put a muzzle on it.
我暂时选择...口套
I've chosen a muzzle... for now.
来的路上我一直在考虑
I was, uh, thinking on the way over here
我不想每次活动都发表同一篇讲话
that I don't wanna do the same speech at every event.
我认为如果每次讲话内容都不同
I really think we'll get more news coverage
能获得更多的媒体关注
if I have a different speech every time.
莉安已经告诉我了
LeAnn already told me.
我做了一些修改
I've been working on some variations.
我觉得我们还得
I think, uh, we also need to
随时对康威的言论作出回应
respond to what Conway is saying...at all times.
开始对他施加压力
Start putting pressure on him.
赛斯的手下会把笔录发给我
Seth's office is sending me transcripts.
《时代周刊》询问可否做采访
There was an interview query from Time,
一条什么纪念基金的语音留言
a voicemail about some memorial fund.
豪斯顿参议员来电确认周二会面的事
Senator Halston called about the meeting on Tuesday.
等等  那条语音留言
Wait. The voicemail.
留言的是劳拉·莫雷蒂
Uh, Laura Moretti,
安东尼·莫雷蒂纪念基金的
from the Anthony Moretti Memorial Fund.
-你之前好像...捐赠过  -帮我调出来
- I guess you... donated? - Cue that up for me.
按1号键就能听了
Just press one when you're ready.
-过会儿再向我汇报  -好的
- I'll catch up with you in a little bit. - Okay.
您好  我是劳拉·莫雷蒂
Hi, this is Laura Moretti
留言给道格拉斯·斯坦普
leaving a message for Douglas Stamper.
我想亲自跟您联系
I just, uh... I wanted to reach out to you personally,
对您的慷慨捐赠表示感谢
to say thank you for the incredibly generous donation.
这是我们收到的最大一笔捐款
It's the biggest donation we've received.
远超其他人
By a lot.
我不知道您是如何知道我们的
Uh, I don't know how you found out about us.
也许是因为总统的移植手术
Maybe because of the President's transplant.
但不论出于何种原因
But whatever the reason,
这对我和孩子们意义非凡
it means so much to us, to me and my children.
不论如何  我知道希望不大
Anyway, I... and I know this is a long shot,
但如果你有空一起喝杯咖啡的话
but if you're ever free for coffee,
我想当面谢谢您
I'd love to thank you in person.
没空...也没关系
No worries if... if you can't.
再次感谢您  斯坦普先生
Um, thanks again, Mr. Stamper.
您好  我是劳拉·莫雷蒂
Hi, uh, this is Laura Moretti
留言给道格拉斯·斯坦普
leaving a message for Douglas Stamper.
我想亲自跟您联系
I just, uh... I wanted to reach out to you personally,
对您的慷慨捐赠表示感谢
to say thank you for the incredibly generous donation.
这是我们收到的最大一笔捐款
It's the biggest donation we've received.
把稿子放到提词器上还来得及吗
Will there be enough time to get this up on the teleprompter?
主要是做了删减
They're mostly cuts.
应该会很快  我这就去
Should be quick. I'll get it there now.
你改了什么
What did you change?
我删去了有关爱的那一段
I took out the paragraph about love.
-那是最精彩的部分  -太软弱了
- That's the best part. - It was too soft.
这儿曾经是家烧烤店
This used to be a barbecue joint, here.
弗兰克当总统前经常光顾
Frank came a lot before he was president.
怎么会变成这样
What happened to it?
弗兰克碰过的东西都是这下场
Same thing that happens to everything Frank touches.
-你介意吗  -介意
- You mind? - I do mind.
我还没答应什么
I haven't agreed to anything yet.
告诉我你知道的事
Tell me what you know.
我知道安德伍德在洗钱的事上撒谎了
I know Underwood lied about the money laundering.
我知道他见了拉尼根  虽然他否认了
I know he met with Lanagin when he said he didn't.
我知道艾德华·密查姆改动了出行记录
I know Edward Meechum doctored travel records,
我还知道那一切你都参与了
and I know you were there for all of it.
然后塔斯克获得赦免  你当上幕僚长
Then Tusk gets a pardon. You get Chief of Staff.
-明日黄花  -你为什么辞职
- Old news. - Why'd you quit the job?
我想回到私营企业
I wanted to go back in the private sector.
你才说过安德伍德碰过的东西都会被毁灭
You just said everything Underwood touches gets demolished.
我不喜欢他  那又怎么样
I don't like the man. So what?
那你为什么在俄罗斯协议上又跟他合作
Why'd you team up with him again for the Russia deal?
我不需要喜欢一起做事的人
I don't have to like the people I work with.
而且  可以狠赚一笔
Plus, there was a fortune to be made.
问题是
See...
我认为你根本不在乎那个钱
I don't think you give a damn about the money.
这里面有其他事  你是不肯承认
There's a lot more to this you're not admitting.
但我认为你想承认
But I think you want to.
那么  你其实没有任何实在的东西
So, truth is, you don't have anything solid.
我会把这事查个水落石出
I will get to the bottom of this story.
我们可以现在谈  或者你可以回头雇一堆律师
We can talk now, or you can wait till you have a team of lawyers
来跟我的事实核查员聊
talking to my fact checkers.
我曾被亿万富翁和总统威胁过
I've been threatened by billionaires and by presidents.
你以为一个失业记者能让我紧张吗
You think an out-of-work reporter makes me nervous?
我现在就可以给白宫打电话
I can call the White House right now,
让他们知道你在调查这件事
let 'em know you're working on this story.
我约你就冒了这个险
That's a gamble I took asking to meet.
但是我赌
But my chips...
你好的一面占上风
are on the better part of you prevailing.
谁  做了什么  为什么  怎么做
The who... the what... the why, how...
别忽略了在哪里做
Don't ignore where.
我觉得转一下会比较好
I think it'd be better if I turn it.
我觉得这一面稍微好点
I think... I think this side is a little better.
-是的  非常漂亮  -弗莱迪
- Yes, that's very nice. - Freddy.
-下午好  总统先生  -下午好
- Good afternoon, Mr. President. - Good afternoon.
海伦在教我做事呢
Helen is teaching me the ropes.
我们不打扰您了  先生
We'll leave you be, sir.
弗莱迪
Oh, Freddy?
你留一下吧  非常感谢
Why don't you stay back for a little bit? Thank you very much.
我马上过去
I'll be right there.
好久不见
It's been a while.
他们  几个月前把我调去了花房
Well, they, uh... moved me to the flower shop a few months ago.
在地下室
The basement.
所以你没怎么见到我
That's probably why you haven't seen me around.
我绝对想不到  居然会喜欢做这个
Never would've guessed that, well, that this would be my thing.
看来老家伙还是能学点新把戏的
I guess you can teach an old dog new tricks.
-你孙子还好吗  -他很好  很好
- How's your grandson? - He's good, good.
刚开始重新上学
Just started school again.
-他读几年级了  -六年级
- What grade is he in now? - Sixth grade.
慢慢长大了
Getting up there.
我真的得走了
I... I really should go.
有一大批秋季的花要送过来
We got a big, uh, shipment of autumn blooms in.
那下次再聊吧
Well, then another time, I guess, maybe.
弗兰克
You know, Frank...
我很快就要走了
I'm gonna be leaving soon.
海伦的丈夫在乔治敦开了一家花店
Helen's husband opened up a flower shop in Georgetown.
他们想要我过去工作
They want me to work there.
你在这里不开心吗  弗莱迪
Well, are you not happy here, Freddy?
该尝试点新东西了
Time to try something new.
我能做点什么说服你留下来吗
Well, is there anything I can do to convince you to stay?
加薪  调整工作时间
A raise? Better hours?
我很感激  但是我已经答应海伦了
I appreciate it, but I've already told Helen yes, and...
而我打算说到做到  那是我想做的
I plan on keeping my word on that. It's what I want.
我会想念你的  弗莱德
Well, I'm gonna miss you around, Freddy.
这里没几个人
There's not many people here...
Well, I guess there aren't that many people here
能让我觉得那么自在
I'm all that comfortable with.
你知道你走之前应该做什么吗
You know what you should do before you go?
你应该哪天晚上上来给我们做一顿肋排
You should come up here one night and cook us a rack of ribs.
我知道烤箱烤的肯定不如碳烤
Now, I realize oven-baked isn't nearly as good as the smoker,
但你怎么样都能做得很美味
but you'd make 'em delicious, anyhow.
肋排  是吗
Ribs? Really?
你想让我给你做肋排吃
You want me to cook ribs for you.
对  就像以前那样  有什么不对吗
Well, sure, just like old times. What's wrong with that?
我只是仆人  对不对
I'm just the help, ain't I?
-不  不是这样的  -我告诉你我遇见了好事
- No, that's not true. - I tell you I got something good going,
而你的第一反应不是
and your first thought ain't,
"弗莱迪  恭喜"
"Freddy, congratulations."
而是"给我做肋排"  对我的盛大欢送
It's "Make me ribs." And what's my big send-off?
-就是给你做肋排  -不
- I get to cook you ribs. - No.
你对这事太过敏感了
Look, you are being way oversensitive about this.
你误解了我的意思
You're misinterpreting what I meant.
你说得对
You're right.
都是我的错
It's all my fault.
-真不知克莱尔是怎么做到的  -你说什么
- I don't know how Claire does it. - What did you just say?
你也这么对她吗  她也是收藏品之一
Is this how you treat her? She part of the collection, too?
我不知道你这怨气从何而来
I don't know where all this is coming from,
但也太忘恩负义了
but it's extremely ungrateful,
想想我为你做了那么多
given all that I have done for you.
你为我做了什么  弗兰克
What did you do for me, Frank?
这里是白宫
This is the White House.
你得叫我"总统先生"
You will call me "Mr. President"!
你就是个王八犊子
You're a motherfucker!
滚
Get out!
我的错  我的错
My bad, my bad.
你是个王八犊子  总统先生
You're a motherfucker, Mr. President!
康威州长一直声称
Governor Conway continues to say
我们在反恐上做得还不够
we're not doing enough about terrorism,
但他忽视了哈里发国已得到遏制的事实
but he ignores the fact that ICO has been stopped in its tracks.
总统不眠不休地与国外敌人作斗争
The president is working tirelessly to combat our enemies abroad,
康威州长的言论
and what Governor Conway lacks in his assessment...
忽略了总统数十年的经验...
is the decades of experience the president brings...
你还应该继续叫他"总统"吗
Do you think you should keep calling him "The president"?
我想强调我们是竞选搭档
Well, I wanna emphasize that we're running mates,
而且莉安告诉我  婚姻角度并不成功
and LeAnn is telling me that the marriage angle isn't working.
别管什么调查
Screw the research.
人们想听见真正的你  有血有肉的人
People want to hear the real you, a real person.
你在党代会上向他们展示的就是真正的你
That's what you gave them at the convention.
抱歉
Sorry.
那情况完全不同
That was very different.
没错  的确不同  那时你是诚恳的
Exactly. It was very different. It was honest.
你不能只机械地回应他的话
And you don't want to just react to what he's saying.
你得拿出点东西来
You wanna offer something.
我跟弗兰西斯一起竞选了三十年
I have been campaigning with Francis for 30 years.
不能让对手骑在你头上
You don't ever let the opponent walk all over you.
如果受到攻击  就得还击
If you're getting attacked, you fight back.
可以  但用另一种方式还击
Fine, but fight back in a different way.
这个人...他都是搞噱头  很肤浅
This guy is... He's all spotlight and surface,
上杂志封面  玩推特  别玩他的游戏
and magazine covers and Twitter. Don't play his game.
压根就别玩  摆脱游戏
Don't play the game at all, please. Get beyond the game.
我们早上再继续做吧
You know what? Let's finish this in the morning, please.
抱歉  你说得对
I'm sorry. You're right.
关于这种事你的经验比我多得多
You have a lot more experience in this kind of thing than I do.
-我应该听你的  -不  我尊重你的反馈
- I should follow your lead. - No, I... I respect your feedback.
感谢你能表现得如此专业
Thank you for being so professional about everything.
-你真体贴  -不是体贴
- You've been very kind. - I'm not kind.
现实而已
Just realistic.
你写的关于爱的那段让我不舒服
That paragraph you wrote about love, it made me uncomfortable.
-说你爱弗兰西斯  -我确实爱他
- Saying you love Francis? - I do love him.
那是什么让你不舒服
Then what made you uncomfortable?
在你面前说出来
Saying it in front of you.
-好吗  -好
- Yes? - Yeah.
-她怎么样  -效果甚微
- How'd she do? - Very little effect.
-新闻上铺天盖地全是她  -白噪音
- She was all over the news. - White noise.
我们怎么深入人心
So how do we make it stick?
我能做的不多
Well, there's not much I can do.
我们给你权限了  我要得到更多结果
We gave you access. I need more than I'm getting.
你应该告诉我人们想要什么
You're supposed to tell me what people want.
人们不知道自己想听爵士
People didn't know they wanted jazz
直到他们第一次听到了爵士乐
until they heard it for the first time.
我能让他们喜欢音乐  但我不能创作音乐
I can get them to like the music. I can't compose it.
你得给我点材料
Give me something I can work with.
我们可以把这事公诸于众吗
Is this something we could take public?
不  这是机密
No, it's classified.
但这太完美了  总统跟俄罗斯人勾结
But it's perfect, the president colluding with the Russians.
这个想法是可行的
The idea has merit.
俄罗斯人门路更广
The Russians will have far more access,
而且也不会置美国军队于危险之中
and it doesn't put American troops in harm's way.
褒奖总统的政策不会让我们得到选票
We don't get votes by praising the president's policy.
让德雷尔在委员会审议中否决它
Let's have Dreyer block it in committee.
虽然我不喜欢总统最初处理哈里发国的方式
I don't like the way the president's handled ICO from the get-go,
但他这次的方法也许会有效
but his approach might work here.
那正是我要防止的
That's what I'm trying to prevent.
你想留哈里发国的领袖一命
So, you wanna keep the ICO leadership alive,
就为了我们能继续拿这个说事
so we can stay on message?
只是拖到11月而已
Just until November,
等我们就职后就狠狠打击他们
and then we'll hit 'em hard after inauguration.
我当初正是为这种扯淡事才辞职
This is the exact sort of BS I resigned over in the first place.
在那边等我一下
I'll see you over there.
再有两个月我们就能获胜
Two months away from winning this thing.
一旦他获得主动权  一旦他获得一点势头
But if he gains the initiative, if he picks up any momentum,
都可能影响我们的胜算
that could put us in the margin of error.
我以为你不一样
I thought you were different.
别胡思乱想  将军
Don't get any ideas, General.
你登上我这艘船
You threw caution into the wind
就已把谨慎抛到九霄云外
when you got yourself on my ticket.
你再做一次  就显得愚蠢了
You do it again, you start to look foolish.
你去跟德雷尔谈谈  让他毙掉这项议案
You talk to Dreyer and 86 this bill.
来到威斯康星州怎能不来尝尝鲜
I couldn't come to Wisconsin without having a taste test.
海耶斯先生  我叫汤姆·汉默施密特
Mr. Hayes. My name's Tom Hammerschmidt.
我是一个自由记者
I'm a freelance reporter.
我想跟你谈谈
I was hoping I could talk to you for a moment.
我不跟记者谈
I don't talk to reporters.
是关于总统的事
It's a story about the president.
你没听到我说什么吗
Did you not hear me the first time?
我认为在你的烧烤店里...曾发生过一些事
I think things happened... in your barbecue place.
会面
Meetings.
你可能顺耳听到过什么
Things you might have overheard.
我觉得总统触犯了法律
I think the president broke the law,
而且我觉得你知情
and I think you know about it.
跟我来  找个没人能听到的地方再聊
Come with me. Let's talk where no one can hear us.
-你带录音笔了吗  -带了
- So, uh, you bring a recorder? - Yeah.
好  我告诉你真相
All right. Here's the truth.
我不再为他工作了  我不再为他烤排骨了
I don't work for him no more. I don't serve him ribs no more.
我不想再跟他有任何关系
I don't want nothing to do with him no more.
即使我恨他  我也的确恨他
Even if I hated him, and I do hate him...
我也不会告密  对警察  对记者
I don't snitch. Not to cops, not to reporters.
对谁都不会
Not to anybody.
离我远点
Leave me the fuck alone.
好了
Okay.
林肯和罗斯福都是共和党的先进分子
Lincoln and Roosevelt were progressive Republicans.
-杰弗逊是一名有远见的保守党  -是的
- Jefferson was a visionary Conservative. - Yeah!
乔治·华盛顿是位强大的领袖
George Washington was a strong commander in chief.
威廉·康威拥有所有这些品质
William Conway embodies all these qualities.
我为背书他竞选总统而骄傲
I proudly endorse his candidacy for president,
我也希望我们州的每个人都这么做
and I ask everyone in our great state to do the same.
欢迎未来的美国总统  威廉·康威
The next President of the United States, William Conway!
你们的支持让我受宠若惊
I'm... I'm humbled by your endorsement,
我身后这些伟人遗留的贡献也让我自愧不如
and by the legacy of these great men behind me.
接任他们是一项艰巨的任务
Now, they all left very big shoes to fill.
知道谁完全没有接任的资格吗
You know who hasn't come even close to filling them?
弗兰克·安德伍德
Frank Underwood.
我该离开
I should go.
我们降落之后
Once we land.
我就飞回东海岸
I'll get a flight back to the East Coast.
-汤姆...  -你不用多说了
- Tom... - You don't have to say anything.
有人向房子扔鸡蛋
We've had eggs thrown at the house.
番茄  牛粪  什么都有
Tomatoes, cow dung. You name it.
南达科他州十分支持康威
South Dakota's big Conway country.
我们一生都住在这儿  也在这儿养育后代
We've been here all our lives. We raised our son here.
从未遇到过这种情况
It's just beyond our experience.
这些人都是我们的邻居
All these folks are our neighbors.
可我一把标志竖起来
But once I put that sign up...
康威州长是退伍军人  而且有孩子
Governor Conway is a veteran. He has children.
为什么选我们  而不是他
Why us and not him?
当我们看到你们两个在党代会
When we saw you two at the convention...
我说不清  看上去真像对儿好搭档
I don't know. It just seemed like a real partnership.
爱  深沉  坚定的爱
Love. Deep, unwavering love.
感谢你们提醒我
I wanna thank you for reminding me
那种爱有多重要
how important that kind of love is.
它真的很重要  我们容易忙于竞选
Because it is. It's easy to get caught up in the campaign
而忘记弗兰西斯和我是怎样走到这一步的
and to forget how Francis and I got here in the first place,
记得我们不仅是总统和第一夫人
to remember that we're not just President and First Lady,
或丈夫和妻子
or husband and wife.
我们是搭档
We're partners.
我们决定要一起解决所有事
We have made a choice to tackle everything together.
我们超越了美丽和完美
We go beyond what's pretty and perfect,
超越了恐惧  困难和未知
beyond what's scary, difficult and unknown.
我们不仅是候选人名单上的搭档
We're not just partners on the ticket.
我们也是生活中的搭档
We're partners in life.
总统先生
Mr. President.
众议院情报委员会里
You have someone on the inside of
有人给你
the House Intelligence Committee
提供机密信息
feeding you classified information.
我是在任州长
I'm a sitting governor.
获得信息没什么错
There's nothing wrong with staying informed.
所有共和党人都在反对俄罗斯的介入
Every Republican is against the Russians being involved.
你是在干预国家安全
You are interfering with national security.
我没摆布任何人
I haven't influenced a single member.
那是因为你让布洛哈特这么做
Oh, that's because you're having Brockhart do it.
如果将军提供专业建议
If the general chooses to share his expertise with them,
他们当然愿意听
they're well served by it.
你每天要说50次我们得摧毁哈里发国
Fifty times a day, you say we should destroy ICO,
现在又故意阻止我们那么做
and now you're deliberately preventing us from doing it.
你6个月前就可以摧毁他们了
You could've destroyed them six months ago,
所以不要把这赖在我...
so don't lay that at my...
我不怪你装相  州长
I don't blame you for being a fraud, Governor.
我们都偶尔要伪善一下
I mean, we all have to be hypocrites, every now and then.
但如果你阻止  我就得派美国军队
But if you block this, I'll send American troops in instead.
你不会派美国人过去的  叙利亚不会同意的
You won't send Americans. Syria won't allow it.
我不在乎叙利亚会不会同意
I don't care what Syria will allow.
但你难道不希望让俄罗斯人去冒险
But wouldn't you rather have it be Russians in harm's way,
而不是美国同胞士兵吗
than your fellow American soldiers?
如果有人牺牲  那将是你一手造成的
If anyone gets killed, that's going to be blood on your hands.
你想让我叫共和党人同意
You want me to tell the Republicans to... get on board.
或让将军去做
Or have the general do it.
把政治放在一边  做正确的事
Put politics aside and do the right thing.
你真以为你这通电话
Did you really think you'd be able to convince me
能说服我吗  总统先生
by making this call, Mr. President?
我领先两位数  我的说法能博取支持
I'm ahead by double digits. I got a message that's working.
你有麻烦  就诉诸于我的责任感
You're on your heels, and you're asking me to help you
想让我帮你
by appealing to my sense of duty?
就连你都信了我的说辞
I've even got you sold on my message.
你不该太相信电视上的东西
Well, you shouldn't believe everything you see on TV.
州长挂电话了  总统先生
The governor has ended the call, Mr. President.
我们走
Let's go.
我们要出动自家的地面部队
We're gonna go forward with our own ground operation.
我去通知参联会  先生  还有件事
I'll inform the Joint Chiefs. Sir, there's another thing.
情报委员会
The Intelligence Committee...
如果康威在内部有人
If Conway has someone on the inside--
你是担心对监控的监督
You're worried about oversight on surveillance.
人们对此更加关注了
There's increased attention.
如果他们打探  发现了麦卡伦做的事
They dig around, find out what Macallan's up to...
我们不是无懈可击吗
Yeah, but I thought we were airtight.
莉安那么说  但还是...
Leann says we are, but still...
最保险的就是了结此事
The safest thing would be to end it.
克莱尔·安德伍德这两天一直在活动
Claire Underwood's been on the move the past two days,
走访康威州长办过活动的每一个州
showing up in every state Governor Conway's held events.
总统却一直缺席
Absent from the trail has been the President.
引用新闻发言人赛斯·格雷森的原话
Press Secretary Seth Grayson said, quote,
"总统目前正在处理
"The President is attending to the business of government
政府事务"
for the time being," end quote.
但他没有表明
But he neglected to say
总统何时会继续竞选
when the President would resume campaigning,
目前竞选网站上
and there are no upcoming events
也没有列出近期活动信息
currently listed on the campaign website,
这让人推测总统缺席的真正原因
leading some to speculate that the real reason for his absence
可能是身体问题
may be health-related.
总统接受肝脏移植已经过去六个月了
It's been six months since the President received a liver transplant.
虽然他可以继续正常...
Although he was able to resume normal...
-你的眼睛怎么了  -弗莱迪·海耶斯干的
- What happened to your eye? - Freddy Hayes.
那他什么都没说了
So I assume he didn't talk.
我需要一个切入点  丹顿先生
I need a way in here, Mr.Danton.
我已经尽力帮你了
I've helped you as much as I can.
我知道你不会公开作证
I know you won't go on record.
我甚至不要求你作为背景出现
I'm not even asking to put you on background.
我只想知道我是接近还是偏离
All I'm looking for is whether I'm warm or cold.
这是什么啤酒
What kind of beer is that?
贮藏啤酒  微酿的...我不知道名字
A lager. Some microbrew they had, um... I don't know the name.
我能尝尝吗
Mind if I try it?
请便
Go ahead.
好喝
It's good.
我年少时候玩过一个喝酒游戏
Used to play a drinking game when I was a teenager...
叫"我从来没有过"
called Never Have I Ever.
-知道那游戏吗  -有过那个经历就喝
- You know that game? - You drink when you have.
就是那个
That's the one.
或者如果总统有过
Or if the President has.
被特别检察官调查的时候
Never have I ever perjured myself
我从来没有做过伪证
when investigated by a special prosecutor.
我从来没有和雷蒙德·塔斯克达成过协议
Never have I ever struck a deal with Raymond Tusk...
让他做伪证换取赦免
to perjure himself in exchange for a pardon.
我从来没有密谋弹劾过总统
Never have I ever conspired to impeach a President
好让我自己当上总统
so I could become President myself.
我们得再叫点酒了
We're gonna need more beer.
-第一夫人在1号线上  先生  -谢谢
- The First Lady is on line one, sir. - Thank you.
克莱尔
Claire.
道格给我打电话说我们要派出自己的军队
Doug called me about sending in our own troops.
要么派出要么无所行动  康威不肯让步
Well, it was that, or sit on our hands. Conway wouldn't budge.
凯茜怎么说
And what does Cathy say?
我更想知道你的想法
I'm more interested in hearing what you think.
我认为...采取点行动总比什么都不做强
Well, I think... doing something is better than doing nothing.
活动怎么样了
How are the events going?
说不好  做了好多场  都分不清了
It's hard to tell. I've done so many, it's all a blur.
今晚只剩一场访谈了
There's only one interview left tonight,
今天就结束了
and then we're done for the day,
但是...明天有七场
but then there's, uh... seven events tomorrow.
你还好吧
How are you holding up?
我想告诉你汤姆不再为选举工作了
I called to tell you Tom's not working on the campaign anymore.
-他辞职了  -不是
- Did he quit? - No.
怎么回事
What happened?
我们俩决定这样最好
We both decided it was for the best.
我们不用担心他  弗兰西斯
We don't have to worry about him, Francis.
你听起来很累
You sound tired.
今晚好好睡一觉吧
Make sure you get a full night's sleep tonight.
-弗兰西斯  -怎么了
- Francis? - Yes?
没事
Nothing.
-明天见  -好的  明天见
- I'll see you tomorrow. - Okay, tomorrow.
-你确定安德伍德知道  -但沃克不知道
- You're certain Underwood knew? - And Walker didn't.
丹顿会不会有什么企图
Could Danton have some agenda on this?
他没有理由撒谎
He has no reason to lie.
除了他还有谁能证实
Who's corroborated, besides him?
没有了  所以我才来这儿
No one. That's why I'm here.
我需要制度支持  律师  调查...
I need institutional support. Legal, research...
还有不会被我的狗干扰的办公地点
a place to work where my dog won't bark at me.
如果能搞定这篇报道  你想做什么都行
If you crack this story, you can do anything you want.
-我还可以让你再当上主编  -我不要
- I'll even make you managing editor again. - I don't want that.
我想要的是...绝对自主权
What I do want... is absolute autonomy.
组建自己的团队  小规模
I build my team, I keep it small,
并且只向你汇报
and I answer only to you.
-人身安全呢  -这只是不走运
- How about security? - Oh, this was just some bad luck.
我已经失去两名记者了  汤姆
I've lost two reporters, Tom.
拜托  玛格丽特
Oh, come on, Margaret.
安德伍德或许是个坏蛋  但他不会杀人
Underwood may be a crook, but he's not a killer.
我也这么看  但我不想冒险
I don't think so either, but I don't wanna take any chances.
你把我要的人找来就好
You just get me the staff I need.
文章一旦发表  就没人能动我了
Once this article comes out, I'm untouchable.
白宫要想挥拳头  就让律师出面
When the White House starts throwing punches... lawyer up.
因为他只能冲着《先驱报》  不能冲我来
'Cause he's gonna throw 'em at the Herald, not me.
我以前的爱好
Hobby I used to have.
莽原之役
The Battle of the Wilderness.
美国内战战役  1864年5月5日至7日
我花了几个月  造了一个模型
I spent months building a model of it.
之后想再造一个  却没有完成
Started another one, but never finished it.
-为什么  -我成了总统
- Why not? - I became president.
时间总不够
Never enough time.
克莱尔知道你叫我过来吗
Does Claire know you asked me here?
不知道
No.
你们不只是玩玩而已吧
It was more than just a fling, wasn't it?
-她怎么说的  -我没问
- How did she describe it? - I didn't ask.
我就不详述细节了
Well, I'm not gonna go into details.
那样对你太失敬
I respect you too much for that.
你们俩从德州回来时
When you two came back from Texas...
我就有所感觉
I had a feeling.
她说  你逗她母亲笑了
She says... you made her mother laugh.
是啊  看来她挺喜欢我
Yeah, I guess she took a liking to me.
上帝  30年来  我从没见那女人笑过
Christ, I haven't seen that woman laugh in 30 years.
因为我不是威胁
I'm just not a threat.
我不做评判  而是接受了她
Just someone who didn't judge, accepted her.
你把克莱尔也逗笑了吗
Do you make Claire laugh?
我们有共鸣
We have a connection.
是的  我也让她笑了
Yeah... I make her laugh.
让她有被渴望的感觉
I make her feel desired.
我觉得她愿意让我看到她脆弱的一面
I think she feels comfortable being vulnerable around me.
我得说  你没生气  让我有些惊讶
I have to say, I'm a bit surprised you're not upset.
-生气有什么好处  -我很钦佩  弗兰克
- What would that achieve? - I admire that, Frank.
我昨天对一个老朋友发火了
I got angry with an old friend yesterday
因为他叫我弗兰克  而不是总统先生
for calling me "Frank" Instead of "Mr. President."
就因为直呼你的名字吗
Just for using your name?
我想不是因为名字
It wasn't the name, I suppose.
而是因为他要离开我了
It's the fact that he's leaving me.
-怎么离开你  -换工作了
- Leaving you how? - New job.
-他本来为你工作吗  -就在白宫
- He worked for you? - Here in the White House.
下属要和上司做朋友不容易
It's tough for employees to be your friends.
所以我决定做个了结
That's why I decided to end it.
-是你要走的  -这样她就不用开口了
- You decided to leave. - So that she wouldn't have to ask me to.
那你的书呢
And what about your book?
我决不会那样背叛她
I would never betray her like that.
谢谢你  汤姆
Thank you, Tom.
-我送你出去  -我自己走就好
- I'll walk you out. - I know my way out.
不过谢了
But thanks.
保重  弗兰克
Take care, Frank.
三支队伍  北面  东面  西面
Three teams. North, east, and west.
我们形成三角攻势  向中心进发
We'll triangulate and advance on the center.
每支队伍都将有一名外勤特工
Each team will have a field agent
与当地人员一同寻找艾哈迈迪兄弟
working with local assets to locate the Ahmadis.
这是行政命令  先生
Here's the executive order, sir.
您希望直接击毙还是活捉
Do you have a preference? Dead or alive?
如果他们能提供情报  就活捉
Alive, if we can get intelligence out of 'em.
-谢谢  先生  -谢谢  先生
- Thank you, sir. - Thank you, sir.
记住  你是在向我汇报
You're officially briefing me
关于哈里发国的监控行动
on ICO-related surveillance activities.
你从未与总统见面或谈话
You never saw or spoke to the President.
走这边
This way.
麦卡伦先生
Mr. Macallan.
-总统先生  -总统在他的宅邸
- Mr. President. - The President's in his residence...
不在这里
not here.
安全问题  我们有些担忧
Security. We have concerns.
康威在众议院情报委员会里有人
Conway has people on House Intelligence.
我把一切都掩盖好了
I've got everything masked.
监控哈里发国和给竞选用的算法完全相同
The algorithms for ICO and the campaign are identical.
只是输入的变量不一样而已
It's just a matter of what variables you input.
说通俗点
Give me English.
一只勺子  我可以用来搅拌咖啡
One spoon. I can use it to stir my coffee...
用来喝汤
to eat soup...
或是加热海洛因
to boil heroin.
他们只能看见勺子  看不见我用它做什么
All they see is the spoon, not what I do with it.
或者我们干脆让勺子消失
Or we could just get rid of the spoon.
关停吗  那太可惜了
Shut it down? Well, that would be a shame,
特别是在昨天之后
especially after yesterday.
-昨天发生了什么  -超越了发生
- What happened yesterday? - Beyond happened.
"超越"
"Beyond"?
你太太在南达科塔州说的话
What your wife said in South Dakota.
"超越美丽和完美"
"Beyond what's pretty and perfect."
摆脱习俗  过往
Liberation from convention, from the past.
超越表面  超越空谈  超越竞选
Beyond surface, beyond bullshit, beyond the election.
-超越婚姻  -正是
- Beyond marriage. - Yes, exactly.
你们不仅是夫妻  不仅是竞选搭档
You're not just husband and wife. You're not just running mates.
你们两者都是  却不止于此
You're both and more.
你们代表了一种可能
You're what's possible.
康维夫妇是梦幻偶像
The Conways are everything everyone wants to be.
但你们才是理想境界
You're everything everyone wants to become.
总统遭到了枪击  做了肝脏移植
The President has been shot. He's had a liver transplant.
我相信匹兹堡的所有人都在想
And I'm sure everyone here in Pittsburgh is wondering,
如果他死了怎么办
what happens if he dies?
无意冒犯  不过...
Not to be indelicate, but...
如果我成了总统吗
What if I became president?
这很合理
And that's fair.
我党选择我  因为他们看到的是
Our party chose me because they saw
一个团队不可分割的一半
one half of an indivisible team.
无条件的支持
Unconditional support.
携手共进多年的两人
Two people working together for years.
相互支撑是一回事
Supporting each other is one thing.
经验是另一回事
Experience is another.
你的经验很少
You have very little.
从你的戒指看得出你结婚了
I can see from your ring that you're married.
是的  18年了
Yes. Eighteen years.
那么你知道什么是真正的搭档
So you know what real partnership is.
我们一起走过了30年
We have 30 years under our belts.
相互学习  相互建议  这就是经验
Learning from and advising each other? I'd call that experience.
好  你们有坚实的婚姻
Okay, so you've got a strong marriage,
但说到你的资历
but in terms of your qualifications--
我想说的是
What... what I'm saying is
我们要超越夫妻关系来看
that we need to get beyond husband and wife.
我们要站在团队的角度看
We need to look at the team.
弗兰西斯在国会和白宫干过
Francis has served in Congress, in the White House.
我经营过大型非盈利机构  做过大使
I've run a major nonprofit. I served as ambassador.
我们曾一起通过立法  制定政策
We have passed legislation, developed policy.
一切都是我们一起做的  每一步都是
We've done all of that together, every step of the way.
所以我们一起竞选是很自然的事
So it's natural that we would run together.
而且我比谁都了解弗兰西斯
And I know Francis better than anyone.
所以  回答你的问题  如果他死了
So, if he died, to answer your question,
还有谁比我更适合实现他的美国计划呢
who better to carry out his plan for America?
操纵
Manipulation.
欺骗
Deception.
腐败
Corruption.
这就构成滥用职权和触犯法律了
That translates to abuse of power and breaking the law.
我们知道是这样  但我们需要确证
We know it's true, but we need corroboration.
要有公开证人  所有事实经过调查
People on record, every fact researched
并且反复核实
and checked and double-checked.
一切讨论内容不得外传
Nothing we discuss leaves this room.
不能透露给朋友  家人
Not your friends, not your family,
或是门外那50个
not the 50 reporters outside that door
想知道我们在这里干什么的记者
who wanna know what we're doing in here.
一旦白宫对我们做的事有一丝察觉
The second the White House gets wind of what we're doing...
他们就会设法让这个报道
they start to make this story...
消失
disappear.
你在电台访问中的表现太出彩了
The radio interview you did was spectacular.
感觉不错
It felt good.
我觉得我们终于找到发力点了
I feel like we're finally tapping into something.
你在南达科塔那对夫妇那里说的话
Was it Tom, what you said in South Dakota,
是汤姆想的吗
with the couple?
我看过视频了
I saw a videotape of it.
核心是的  然后...
The core of it, yes. And then...
我自己编了一些
I sort of made it my own.
他应该留下
He should stay on.
-不  -不是作为你的讲稿撰稿人
- No. - Not as your speechwriter.
我的意思是  对外人来说
Well, I mean, yes, to the rest of the world,
他还是我们的讲稿撰稿人
he can be our speechwriter.
但这不是他应该留下来的原因
But that's not why he should stay on.
他应该留下来  因为...
He should stay on because...
他能给你我给不了的东西
he can give you things that I can't.
克莱尔  我们一直是个强大的团队
Look, Claire, we've been a great team.
但是一个人...
But one person...
一个人终究不能给另一个人一切
one person cannot give everything to another person.
我不能和你一起旅行
I can't travel with you.
不能在夜里给你温暖
I don't keep you warm at night.
也不能像他那样看待你
I don't see you the way he sees you.
这事不由我允许  但是...
It-- Look, it's not my permission to give, but...
你会做对自己正确的事
you'll do what's right for you.
但我想让你知道  如果你想...
But I want you to know, if you want it...
我知道你会小心的...
I know you'll be careful...
我不介意
and I'll be fine.
如果我们要超越婚姻  那就超越吧
I mean, if we're gonna go beyond marriage, let's go beyond it.
您有三条已存留言
You have three saved messages.
第一条信息  9月8日
Message one. September 8th--
您好  我是劳拉·莫雷蒂  留言给道格拉斯...
Hi, uh, this is Laura Moretti leaving a message for Douglas--
保存留言请按8
To save this message, press eight.
回拨请按5
To call back, press five.
如
To-- -
抱歉  我的保姆到晚了...
I'm sorry. Uh, my sitter was late, and, um...
-路上堵车  -放松
- and then there was traffic, so-- - Just relax.
没关系
It's fine.
很高兴能见到您本人
It's so nice to meet you in person.
给
Here.
我也不知道为什么买了花  我大概...
I don't know why I got them. I guess I, uh...
-总之  -真美  谢谢
- Anyway. - No, they're lovely. Thank you.
还有...再次感谢您...给我们捐款
And, uh... and thank you again... for that donation.
我无法表达这对我们多重要
I just... I can't tell you how much it means--
在语音留言里  还有之前通话时
You already thanked me on your voice message
你已经谢过我了
and when we talked on the phone.
不用再感谢了
You don't need to thank me anymore.
好  不说谢谢了
Okay, no more thanks.
希望这个地方还行
I hope this place is okay.
不是什么高档餐厅  但我常来
It's nothing fancy, but I come here a lot.
我喜欢  挺有个性的地方
I like it. It has a lot of character.
东尼喜欢这种小餐馆
Tony liked greasy spoons like this.
他以前每周日下午
He used to take the kids to,
都带孩子们去宾士红辣碗餐馆
Ben's Chili Bowl every Sunday afternoon
买热狗给他们吃
and get them hot dogs.
抱歉
Sorry.
没事
Don't be.
我也许不该谈我丈夫
I probably just shouldn't talk about my husband.
我还是会控制不住情绪
I still get emotional.
你可以谈...如果你想谈的话
You can... if you want to.
哪怕我哭
Even if I cry?
我想多了解他
I wanna know more about him.
能关一下门吗
Will you close the doors, please?
他在哪
Where is he?
我两天来了这里两次
Twice in two days I've been here.
我知道
I know.
为什么叫我来
So, why am I here now?
我希望你回来
I want you back.
我也是
I want you back, too.
但是...
But...
他理解
He understands.
从美国首位第一夫人玛莎·华盛顿
到现在住在白宫的米歇尔·奥巴马
美国历史上出现过很多杰出的第一夫人
她们不仅能在政务上辅佐自己的丈夫
成为总统的诤友良伴
更有几位还凭借非凡的才能和魅力
在美国历史上留下了自己的印记
无论是比尔·克林顿两番问鼎白宫  还是希拉里·克林顿两次参选总统
他们一直都携手作战  既是夫妻  也是战友
在希拉里08年失败的总统竞选  和目前正在进行的大选中
她都将比尔·克林顿作为一件终极武器
因为比尔虽然离任多年  但在美国选民中一直有着非常高的支持率
但终极武器使用不当  也会事倍功半
比如在08年的选举中
媒体就认为比尔·克林顿过度攻击奥巴马  招致黑人选民反感
这对希拉里的失败要负有一定责任
在目前正在进行的选举中  比尔·克林顿也十分卖力
希拉里在初选初期凯歌高奏  比尔功不可没
而在生活中  由于希拉里离开白宫后  有了自己的事业  同比尔聚少离多
很多人认为  两人更像是政治盟友
希拉里对比尔继续拈花惹草的绯闻并不在意